{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Hot Tub \u0026 Spa Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40088/":{"taskOID":40088,"originalTaskOID":40088,"setID":400,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5583,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Hot Tub or Spa","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of hot tub or spa needs to be repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2635,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Free-standing (portable)","answerDisplayText":"Free-standing (portable)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1176,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Built-in (in-ground)","answerDisplayText":"Built-in (in-ground)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1324,"questionDisplayText":"Problem description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What describes the problem with your hot tub or spa? (Choose all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2955,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Heater not working","answerDisplayText":"Heater not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3384,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Jets not working","answerDisplayText":"Jets not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Filtration system needs cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Filtration system needs cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2670,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Frozen water","answerDisplayText":"Frozen water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4224,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"No power to system","answerDisplayText":"No power to system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6531,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Tub is dirty","answerDisplayText":"Tub is dirty","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3606,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Lights not working","answerDisplayText":"Lights not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1672,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cover needs replacing","answerDisplayText":"Cover needs replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6208,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Surface is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Surface is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5583,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Hot Tub or Spa","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of hot tub or spa needs to be repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2635,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Free-standing (portable)","answerDisplayText":"Free-standing (portable)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1176,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Built-in (in-ground)","answerDisplayText":"Built-in (in-ground)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2635,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Free-standing (portable)","answerDisplayText":"Free-standing (portable)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1176,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Built-in (in-ground)","answerDisplayText":"Built-in (in-ground)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1324,"questionDisplayText":"Problem description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What describes the problem with your hot tub or spa? (Choose all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2955,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Heater not working","answerDisplayText":"Heater not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3384,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Jets not working","answerDisplayText":"Jets not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Filtration system needs cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Filtration system needs cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2670,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Frozen water","answerDisplayText":"Frozen water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4224,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"No power to system","answerDisplayText":"No power to system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6531,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Tub is dirty","answerDisplayText":"Tub is dirty","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3606,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Lights not working","answerDisplayText":"Lights not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1672,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cover needs replacing","answerDisplayText":"Cover needs replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6208,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Surface is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Surface is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2955,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Heater not working","answerDisplayText":"Heater not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3384,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Jets not working","answerDisplayText":"Jets not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Filtration system needs cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Filtration system needs cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2670,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Frozen water","answerDisplayText":"Frozen water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4224,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"No power to system","answerDisplayText":"No power to system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6531,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Tub is dirty","answerDisplayText":"Tub is dirty","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3606,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Lights not working","answerDisplayText":"Lights not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1672,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cover needs replacing","answerDisplayText":"Cover needs replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6208,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Surface is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Surface is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40088/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40088,"taskName":"Hot Tub or Spa - Repair or Service","taskDescription":"Repair or Service a Hot Tub or Spa","xmTaskDescriptor":"Hot Tub \u0026 Spa Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":132,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Hot Tub jacuzzi parts Spa","textMessagingName":"Svc Hot Tub","rolloverLongDesc":"These systems often include a tub, jets, heater, pump, bubbler \u0026 filter. Problems may include both electrical \u0026 plumbing issues. Usually handled by spa specialists.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes stand-alone wooden or fiberglass tubs.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Service a Hot Tub or Spa.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Hot Tub \u0026 Spa Repair Services","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":45,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Hot Tub or Spa Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Hot Tub or Spa - Repair or Service","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Hot Tub or Spa Repair Project","urlName":"Hot-Tub-or-Spa-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Hot Tub \u0026 Spa Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Hot,Tub,jacuzzi,parts,Spa,tubs,sauna,spas","emcCategoryOid":-12044,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":400,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}